{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51622794","name":"Spread Deli","address":"4215 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","owner":"Tersion Yatooma","licenseNumber":"230530","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"Medium","reviewFrequencyDays":"365.0","coords":"-83.06370,42.35066","geojson":{"id":"51622794","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.063696815,42.3506572850001]},"properties":{"name":"Spread Deli","owner":"Tersion Yatooma","address":"4215 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"Medium","license_number":"230530","establishmentid":"51622794","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"365.0","most_recent_license_date":"10/26/2018"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"5380","name":"Alley Taco","address":"418 Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622811","name":"Avalon International Breads","address":"422 W Willis St","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622620","name":"Cobb Corner Bar","address":"4201 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5056","name":"Treat Dreams","address":"4160 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5386","name":"Detroit Royale with Cheese","address":"4163 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4608","name":"Go! Sy Thai","address":"4240 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622479","name":"Tou & Mai","address":"4240 Cass Ave, Ste. 102","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"51622641","name":"Fresh 101 Superfood Cafe","address":"4240 Cass Ave Ste. 100","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"4646","name":"La Feria Spanish Tapas","address":"4130 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"},{"establishmentid":"5042","name":"Slows On The Go Mobile Kitchen","address":"4107 Cass Ave","zipcode":"48201"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"48800","inspectionDate":"2019-07-24T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"No","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-501.16","violationDescription":"Except during preparation, cooking, or cooling, or when time is used as the public health control POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD) shall be maintained:\r\n(A)  135ºF or above, except that roasts properly cooked and cooled may be held              at a temperature of 130ºF; or (P)\r\n(B)   At 41ºF or less (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Cold food item(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored above 41 degrees F","subProblem":"","location":"COOKING/PREP AREA","subLocation":"Cooler (deli case)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"8-301.11","violationDescription":"A PERSON may not operate a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT without a valid PERMIT to operate issued by the REGULATORY AUTHORITY.","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Retail food service establishment","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not available","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"No","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-903.11","violationDescription":"Cleaned EQUIPMENT and UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES shall be stored in an approved manner and location.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Clean equipment/utensil(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored on floor or less than 6 inches above floor","subProblem":"","location":"KITCHEN","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"5-205.15","violationDescription":"A PLUMBING SYSTEM shall be:\r\n(A) Repaired according to LAW; (P) and\r\n(B) Maintained in good repair.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Plumbing system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not maintained","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null}]},{"inspectionid":"44643","inspectionDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"3-101.11","violationDescription":"FOOD shall be safe, unADULTERATED and honestly presented. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Food","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not safe","subProblem":"","location":"FACILITY","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-27T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Discard."},{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Water source and system","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM (UNISEX)","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2019-07-24T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient water pressure to meet demand of use."}]},{"inspectionid":"44031","inspectionDate":"2018-10-30T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Plan Review/Pre-Open","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"5-103.11","violationDescription":"(A) The water source and system shall be of sufficient capacity to meet the peak water demands of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n(B) Hot water generation and distribution systems shall be sufficient to meet the peak hot water demands throughout the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Hot water supply","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Insufficient to meet demands","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"At the Three compartment sink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide sufficient supply if hot water such as a larger or additional hot water heater."},{"violationCode":"5-501.16","violationDescription":"(A) An inside storage room and area and outside storage area and enclosure, and receptacles shall be of sufficient capacity to hold REFUSE, recyclables, and returnables that accumulate.   \r\n(B) A receptacle shall be provided in each area of the FOOD ESTABLISHMENT or PREMISES where REFUSE is generated or commonly discarded, or where recyclables or returnables are placed.   \r\n(C) If disposable towels are used at handwashing lavatories, a waste receptacle shall be located at each lavatory or group of adjacent lavatories.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"4-501.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT shall be maintained in a state of repair and condition that meets the requirements of the code.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Cooler (display)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-201.16","violationDescription":"(A) Wall and ceiling covering materials shall be attached so that they are EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) Except in areas used only for dry storage, concrete, porous blocks, or bricks used for indoor wall construction shall be finished and SEALED to provide a SMOOTH, nonabsorbent, EASILY CLEANABLE surface.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall/ceiling covering(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not attached","subProblem":"","location":"DISHWASHING AREA","subLocation":"Near the Handsink","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Securely attach to wall/ceiling."},{"violationCode":"6-201.17","violationDescription":"(A) Except as otherwise allowed by law, attachments to walls and ceilings such as light fixtures, mechanical room ventilation system components, vent covers, wall mounted fans, decorative items, and other attachments shall be EASILY CLEANABLE.\r\n(B) In a CONSUMER area, wall and ceiling surfaces and decorative items and attachments that are provided for ambiance need not meet this requirement if they are kept clean.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Wall attachment(s)","subItem":"ventilation system components","problemDescription":"Not easily cleanable","subProblem":"","location":"SERVICE AREA","subLocation":"At the Ceiling (s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30.0","correctedDate":"2018-11-02T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Repair/replace to be easily cleanable."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2019-10-31T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51622794"}}